Subindex build by Linnet
http://linnet.126.com  http://blog.csdn.net/redbirdli
火鸟字幕合并器SubindexV0.5
Created time 09.09.08 00:15:54
-嗨,瑞秋 -嗨
-Oh! Hey, Rach! -Hi.
-情人节快乐 -你也是
-Happy VaIentine's Day! -You too!
跟罗斯住的感觉如何?
How's Iiving at Ross'?
很不错,只不过他逼我们 整天看探索频道
It's good, except he makes us watch the Discovery ChanneI aII day Iong.
一个在中世纪的丑八怪 发生了一件很无聊的事
Something reaIIy boring happened to someone ugIy in the MiddIe Ages.
谢谢 待会见
Oh, thank you. I'II see you guys Iater.
那是一杯幸运的外带咖啡
That is one Iucky to-go cup of coffee.
我希望你能忘了她 我讨厌看到你这个样子
I wish you wouId get over her. I hate seeing you Iike this.
有什么我能帮上忙的吗? 你要看看我的胸部吗?
Is there anything I can do for you? Do you wanna Iook down my top?
谢谢,或许待会再说吧
Thanks. Maybe Iater.
-阿甘,我能吃饼干吗? -你要什么?
-Gunther, can I get a scone? -Want anything?
我要很多东西
I want a Iot of things.
我希望跟我爱的女人 共度情人节
I wanna be with the woman I Iove on VaIentine's Day.
我希望她也爱我
I want her to Iove me back.
我希望能忘记 无法满足渴望的悲伤
And I want reIief from the wrenching pain of knowing that won't happen!
我们有红色贝果
We have red bageIs.
好吧
Okay.
片名:六人行 生产录影带
你们一起住 到目前为止还好吧?
So how do you guys Iike Iiving together so far?
-很不错 -对
-Oh, it's been good. -Yeah.
只不过罗斯比你更在乎饼干碎屑
Except Ross is more uptight about crumbs than you are.
沙发上有根鸡腿
There was a drumstick in the couch.
我不讨在乎饼干碎屑
And I am not uptight about crumbs.
只不过…
It's just that, you know...
饼干碎屑会引来老鼠 老鼠会随地大便
...crumbs attract mice. And mice Ieave droppings.
黑死病就是那样传染开的
And that's how the pIague started.
如果你希望那种事再发生…
So you wanna reIive that again....
老鼠不会散布黑死病
Mice didn't start the pIague.
是野鼠才会
Rats did.
正确地来说是有病菌的野鼠
Rattus norvegicus, to be exact.
天啊,罗斯
Oh, good God, Ross.
偶尔让我们看点卡通
Nick at Nite, once in a whiIe.
好吧,我要走了 再见
AII right, I'm going. Bye.
菲比,能在这里等一下吗?
Phoebe, wiII you wait here?
-我想听听你的意见 -好的
-I wanna get your opinion on something. -Yeah.
制片:温蒂诺勒
How does Mona feeI about RacheI moving in?
蒙娜对瑞秋搬过去 有什么看法?
我正要告诉她
I'm on my way to teII her.
编剧:戴娜克莱恩布考
She's been away aII week, but she'II be cooI.
她一整个星期都不在 但她会接受的
导演:凯文布莱特
She's been so supportive.
她一直都很支持我
She even got the baby a T-shirt that says ''FossiIs are my friends.''
她甚至帮宝宝买了 写着“化石是我朋友”的上衣
少来了,蒙娜,别拍马屁
Come on, Mona. Don't kiss ass.
我得走了
So I'm gonna take off.
快点 瑞秋想看这卷录影带
Oh, shoot! Oh, shoot! RacheI wanted to see this tape.
-那是什么? -我朋友生孩子的录影带
-What is it? -My friend giving birth.
你能把它带回家吗?
CouId you take it to your apartment?
“糖果跟饼干”?
''Candy and Cookie''?
糖果是妈妈 饼干是女貌
Candy's the mom, Cookie's the daughter.
她爸爸也叫饼干
The father's name is aIso Cookie.
为什么我会跟这些人做朋友?
Why am I friends with these peopIe?
菲比,过来
Phoebe, come here.
我要你看看 浴室里的一样东西
I wanna show you something in the bathroom.
摩妮卡,成熟一点
Monica, grow up.
-你的背后藏了什么东西? -我希望菲比能给点意见
-What's behind your back? -Something I want Phoebe's opinion on.
-你不要我的意见? -我不要
-You don't want my opinion? -Not reaIIy.
少来了,我是你哥哥 问我吧
Come on, I'm your oIder brother. Ask me.
好吧,哥哥
Okay, big brother.
你觉得哪一件能让你朋友 想上你妹妹?
Which one wouId make your best friend want to do your IittIe sister?
红色那件
The red one.
嘿
Hey.
我知道你很沮丧 所以我带了一个东西来帮你打气
I know you're depressed, so I brought someone to cheer you up.
Right outside is a reaI, Iive, furry pIaymate.
我不要 再跟你朋友珍上床
I'm not sIeeping with your friend Jane again.
是小狗
Hey, a dog!
你得承认
Who, you gotta admit, Iooks a Iot Iike Jane.
He's the happiest dog ever. I borrowed him from my friend Wendy.
你可以留下 直到你再打起精神来
So you can keep him tiII he cheers you up.
我自己常借用…
I borrow him myseIf from time to time...
只要我心情不好 想到…
...when I get depressed thinking about...
世界饥荒跟贫穷问题…
...worId hunger, poverty....
不是说你的痛苦微不足道
Not to triviaIize your pain.
谢谢你,菲比 我们一定会玩得很开心
Thanks so much, Pheebs. We are gonna have so much fun!
不是那种开心
Oh, not that kind of fun.
情人节快乐
Happy VaIentine's!
我穿上不是很舒服 但是很放荡的东西
I'm sIipping into something a bit Iess comfortabIe and a bit more sIutty.
“糖果跟饼干”?
''Candy and Cookie''?
''Candy and Cookie''?!
摩妮卡帮我租色情片?
Monica got me porn?
女同志的片子?
GirI-on-girI porn?!
她一定很爱我
She reaIIy must Iove me!
-好吧,放轻松 -我爱你,圣范伦铁诺
-Yeah, just relax. -I Iove you, St. VaIentine.
那真的不太好看
Whoa, whoa, that's not pretty.
用力推
Now push!
天啊,好痛
Oh, God, it hurts!
这是最难看的色情片 这是最难看的色情片
Worst porn ever! Worst porn ever!
-快停下来 -我在弄了
-Oh, make it stop! -I am trying!
去接球,准备好了吗?去接球
Get the baII. Ready? Get the baII!
你很可爱,但你不太聪明
You're cute, but you're not too smart.
我刚丢了这个?
Did I just throw this?
-嗨 -嗨
-Hi. -Hi.
我不小心把这些 跟我的东西混在一起
I accidentaIIy packed these with my stuff.
-是谁? -菲比朋友的狗
-Who is this? -Phoebe's friend's dog.
我不知道叫什么名字 我叫莫查利拉起司
I don't know his reaI name. I caII him MozzareIIa.
你好可爱,我希望能留下来玩 但我得去上班
You are so cute. I wish I couId pIay, but I've gotta go to work.
我希望开会时 我不会这样说话,对,没错
I hope I stop taIking Iike this before my meeting. Yes, I do.
再见,乔伊 说真的,我改不过来
Bye-bye, Joey. SeriousIy, I can't stop it.
过来
Come here! Hey!
她是瑞秋,以前她住在这里
That's RacheI. She used to Iive here.
老实跟你说 我们爱她
Might as weII be honest with you. We Iove her.
但我们不能拥有她
But we can't have her.
我真的想念她
I reaIIy miss her.
你了解吧? 你是男生
Hey, you understand, right? You're a guy.
你以前是的
WeII, you used to be.
你觉得怎样?
So, what do you think?
我还是很辣
I've stiII got it.
-你为什么要给我这个? -那是什么?
-Why did you get me this? -What is it?
里面全是尖叫,鲜血跟扩张的阴道
It's yeIIing, bIeeding, diIating.
扩张的阴道
Oh, the diIating!
这是纪录生产的录影带? 它是菲比的,你为什么要看它?
Is this the video of the birth? It's Phoebe's. Why were you watching it?
我以为或许你会在情人节 帮我租色情片
I thought maybe you got me porn for VaIentine's Day.
如果你以为我会在情人节 帮你租色情片…
If you thought I was gonna get you porn for VaIentine's Day...
那么你说对了
...you were right.
片中的女主角 跑到大都市来追寻星梦…
It's about a girI who moves to the city in search of stardom...
最后她跟很多男人 上床
...but ends up having sex with a Iot of guys.
它有四星级的评价
It got four stars.
等一下,根本没有那种事
Wait a minute. Those aren't stars.
-总之你要看一下吗? -喔…
-Anyway, you wanna take a Iook? -WeII....
-我真的没心情做爱 -发生了什么事?
-I'm not reaIIy in a sexy mood. -Hey, what's going on?
还记得你第一次 看大白鲨…
Remember the first time you saw Jaws...
你花了多少时间 才敢再下水游泳?
...how Iong it took to go back in the water?
我们不能让这卷录影带 毁了情人节
We can't Iet this tape wreck VaIentine's Day.
你得克服它
You gotta get past it.
重振雄风
Just get back on the horse.
不然我要回房 换上我的运动裤
Otherwise, the horse is gonna go into the bedroom and change into her sweatpants.
-好吧,你不知道,你没有看到它 -生孩子的过程很美
-Okay, you don't know. You didn't see it. -ChiIdbirth is beautifuI.
很美?真的吗?
Oh, beautifuI? ReaIIy?
你觉得这很美吗?
You think this is beautifuI?
天啊 难怪我妈恨我
Oh, my God! No wonder my mother hates me!
甜心， 别碰我
-See, honey, there's-- -Don't touch me!
-嗨 -嘿
-Hi! -Hey!
-亚特兰大好玩吗? -很好玩
-How was AtIantic City? -Good.
我帮你买了礼物
I brought you back a present.
你不必…
You didn't have to--
咸水太妃糖?
SaItwater taffy?!
谢谢
Thanks.
有趣的是 它没有加任何海水
InterestingIy, it isn't made with seawater.
事实上 它是用加盐淡水做的
It's actuaIIy made with saIted fresh water.
那一点都不有趣
That's not interesting.
-我觉得很有趣 -我也是,我想你
-I think it's interesting. -Me too. I missed you!
我也是
Me too.
-这星期你过得如何? -非常好
-How was your week? -Good.
-宝宝开始会踢人了 -太棒了
-The baby started kicking. -How exciting!
太神奇了 只不过第一次我并不在场
It was amazing. The onIy thing is, I wasn't there the first time.
-不 -我错过了所有的过程
-Oh, no. -I was missing out on aII this stuff.
-乔伊建议瑞秋搬过来跟我住 -想得美
-Joey suggested RacheI move in with me. -Yeah, right.
-什么? -乔伊害我笑得肚子痛
-What? -Joey cracks me up.
“让你的前妻搬进去 那一点也不别扭”
''Have your ex-wife move in. That wouIdn't be awkward.''
想像我离开了几天…
Imagine, I go away for a few days...
我男朋友跟怀了他孩子的女人 住在一起
...and my boyfriend is Iiving with a woman he got pregnant.
你怎么跟他说?
So, what'd you teII him?
你没有告诉蒙娜 瑞秋搬过去了?
You didn't teII Mona RacheI moved in?
她似乎觉得 那是个疯狂的点子
She seemed to think it was such a crazy idea.
而且她送我太妃糖
PIus, she got me taffy.
-真的吗?我没吃过太妃糖 -真的?
-ReaIIy? I've never had any. -Ever?
我妈忙着计画自杀 没空买海滩小吃给我
My mom was too busy pIanning her suicide to provide saItwater treats.
谢谢
Thank you.
你要告诉她吗?
Are you gonna teII her?
我想我得先哄哄她
I wiII. I want to butter her up first.
我要带她去吃晚餐 做一些浪漫的事
I'm gonna take her to dinner, do aII this romantic stuff.
当她觉得 我是有史以来最棒的男朋友时…
When she thinks I'm the best boyfriend ever...
我会告诉她我怀孕的前女友 跟我一起住
...I'II teII her my pregnant ex-girIfriend is Iiving with me.
或许我没有说过 她是个非常幸运的女人
If I haven't said it before, she's a Iucky, Iucky Iady.
我们… 这个玩意怎么了?
So where are--? What the crap is up with this stuff?
它是口香糖吗?它是食物吗? 怎么了?
Is it gum? Is it food? What's the deaI?
好好吃 我能试试粉红色的吗?
Oh, it's nice. May I try a pink one?
我得计画 这个完美的夜晚
So I just have to pIan the perfect night.
你最棒的约会经验 是什么?
Hey, what's the best date you ever had?
去年葛瑞格海曼 带我去吃很好吃的寿司大餐
Last year, Greg Hayman took me to a very nice sushi dinner.
我们散步 到附近的研究室…
Then we took a romantic waIk to a nearby research Iab...
我们闯进里面 放走二十只猴子
...where we trashed the pIace and freed 20 monkeys.
我就知道 我就知道我没有发疯
I knew it! I knew I wasn't crazy!
去年的确有一只猴子 在公车站攻击我
Last year, a monkey did attack me at the bus stop!
她跟我是朋友 她跟罗斯交往过…
So between her and me being friends, and her history with Ross...
这种事绝不能发生
...it just isn't gonna happen.
那就像是 你爱上一只猫
It'd be Iike you faIIing in Iove with a cat.
-嘿 -嘿
-Hey. -Hey.
我最喜欢的狗怎么了?
How's my favorite dog, huh? How's my favorite dog?
你太压抑了
You're subdued.
-你让喝啤酒了? -不
-Did you give him a beer? -No.
-对不起,我们需要谈一谈 -当然
-WiII you excuse us? We need to taIk. -Sure.
我,对
Oh, me, right.
-很难过,是怎么了? -没事
-He's miserabIe. What happened to him? -Nothing.
-我们聊了一些事 -什么事?
-We taIked about stuff. -What stuff?
关于瑞秋的事
RacheI stuff.
乔伊,你害得很难过
Oh, Joey, you bummed him out! This is the happiest dog in the worId.
He spends a day with you, and Iook!
He's breathing.
好吧,在看着我们 表现的快乐一点,好吗?
Okay, weII, he's watching us so just Iook happy, okay?
-我要带去温蒂家 -很好
-I'II take him to Wendy's. -He's fine.
你看
Look.
快接球
Here's your baII!
去接球 去接球
Get your baII! Get your baII!
去…
Get--
当然
Of course.
你不要网球
You don't want a tennis baII.
因为你可以吃肉球
Not when you can have a meatbaII.
来吧,去接肉球
Come on, get the meatbaII.
天啊,我对你做了什么?
God, what have I done to you?
我害死那只狗了,菲比 我把弄得精神崩溃了
I broke the dog, Pheebs! I broke the dog!
谢谢
Thanks.
我要去接蒙娜 今晚你要做什么?
I'm going to pick up Mona. What are you doing tonight?
我有很棒的情人节计画
Oh, I got big VaIentine's pIans.
我订了中国菜 还有你的咸水太妃糖
I got my Chinese food on the way, and your saItwater taffy.
真有趣 它没有加海水…
InterestingIy, it isn't made with seawater--
我们是一起 看那部纪录片的
We actuaIIy watched the documentary together.
我的外卖来了 我去拿钱
Oh, my Chinese food. I'II get my cash.
蒙娜
Mona?
什么… 嗨,你好吗?
What are--? Hi! How are you?
我应该去接你的
I'm supposed to pick you up.
我帮你做了情人节晚餐 大惊喜
I made you a VaIentine's dinner. Surprise!
-蒙娜 -嗨,瑞秋
-Oh! Hey, Mona! -Hi, RacheI.
她在这里做什么?
What's she doing here?
我不知道
I have no idea.
如果你们要找我 我在房里看电视
I'II be watching TV if anybody needs me.
她在做什么?
What is she doing?
最近 她喜欢待在这里
LateIy she just Iikes hanging out here.
-为什么? -我想她很寂寞
-Why? -I think she's IoneIy.
但今天是情人节 我们能请她离开吗?
But it's VaIentine's Day. Can't we ask her to go?
不行,她太激动了
WeII, no, she's way too emotionaI.
我是说她疯了
And by emotionaI, I mean crazy!
我的外卖来了
That's just my Chinese food.
她叫外卖送到这里来?
She has food deIivered here?
对,她很激动,但她大胆
Yes, she's emotionaI, but baIIsy.
我要去换运动服 躺在床上吃饭
I'm gonna get in my sweats and eat this in bed.
你还以为 她会妨碍到我们
And you thought she was gonna be in our way!
打开香槟 我马上回来
Open the champagne, and I wiII be right back.
-我有大惊喜 -你另一个前妻也藏在里面?
-I've got a surprise. -You got another ex-wife back there?
请开始喝香槟
PIease start drinking.
-我只是要打电话 -瑞秋,等一下
-I'm just gonna grab the phone. -RacheI, wait.
我希望 你不会误会
I hope you don't take this the wrong way.
-你在做什么? -你要打电话吗?
-What are you doing? -Do you need the phone?
不
No.
罗斯太好心了没办法说出口 但这是他的公寓
Ross is too nice to say it, but this is his apartment.
我们需要隐私 你为什么不回你家呢?
We need boundaries, so why don't you go back to your pIace.
蒙娜,我住在这里
But, Mona, I Iive here.
情人节快乐
Happy VaIentine's Day!
或者这能让你在分手后记得我
Or, something to remember me by.
-这次是多久? -九十秒
-How Iong has it been this time? -Ninety seconds.
九十秒没想到它 真的很久
Ninety seconds is a Iong time not to think about it.
但我满脑子都是它
Except aII I did was think about it.
我知道,我也忘不了
I know. It haunts me.
在这之前我看过最糟糕的事 是我爸跟服务生上床
TiII now, the worst thing I'd seen was my dad doing shots off the houseboy.
在这之后我会很乐意 把他们的照片做成银幕保护程式
After this, I wouId gIadIy make that my screen saver.
我们得忘了这件事 我们得假装它不存在
We have to get past this. We'II pretend it never existed.
我可以那么做
I couId do that.
我们只需要 丢掉那张椅子
Now aII we gotta do is get rid of this chair.
-谢天谢地 -我知道
-Oh, thank God! -I know.
请进
Come in!
我很抱歉 破坏了你们的情人节
Hi. I'm sorry to barge in on your VaIentine.
我得远离那些叫骂声 蒙娜要跟罗斯分手
I had to get away from the yeIIing. Mona's dumping Ross.
-天啊 -可怜的罗斯
-Oh, my God. -Poor Ross.
我们看过他穿内裤做瑜珈 但这次他更惨
We watch him do yoga in his underwear, but for this he cIoses the drapes.
关于那卷 你想看的生产录影带
You know that birthing tape you wanted to see?
它在这里
It's here.
我们得在你看它之前警告你 千万别看它
We shouId warn you before you watch it. Don't watch it.
你们看过了?很可怕吗?
You saw it? Is it scary?
讽刺的是 生孩子的画面…
It's ironic how footage of someone being born...
让人想要自杀
...can make you want to kiII yourseIf.
甜心,她不必看它 但她非生孩子不可
Honey, she may not have to watch it but she's going to have to do it.
现在我吓坏了 你们能跟我一起看吗?
Now I'm aII freaked out. WiII you watch it with me?
不,但我会把有我体味的毛衣 放在你旁边
No, but I'II Ieave a sweater that smeIIs Iike me right next to you.
摩妮卡,少来了 你想生孩子
Monica, come on. You want to have kids.
没错
I do.
但送子鸟 会把宝宝送来给我
But the stork is gonna bring mine.
说真的 你们不能逼我一个人看这个
SeriousIy, you're not gonna make me watch this aIone.
她说的对,当然不行
She's right. Of course not.
甜心,去拿录影带
Honey, get the tape.
这让我想起了 录影带里某一段内容
This reminds me of a very specific part of the tape.
当然,如果你把鸡腿放在那里 你是个烂室友
Oh, sure. But if you Ieave a drumstick under there and you're a bad roommate.
来吧
Here we go.
好吧
Okay.
天啊
Oh, my.
加油
Come on, come on.
为什么宝宝要折磨那个女人?
Why is that baby torturing that woman?
为什么我要看这个玩意三次?
Why have I seen this thing three times?
好美
It's beautifuI.
-好可怕 -我知道,我为你感到难过
-It's horribIe! -I know, I know! I'm so sorry for you!
我该怎么办?我不要做这个 我要怎么把宝宝丢掉?
What do I do? I don't want to do this! How do I get out of it?
-大家快看 -什么?她的屁股爆炸了吗?
-You guys! You guys, Iook! -What? Did her ass expIode?
不,宝宝出来了,你们看
No, the baby's out. Look.
看看那些小手指跟小脚趾
Look at those IittIe fingers and toes.
看看妈妈现在有多高兴
Look how happy the mom is now.
-瑞秋 -去你们的,你们不必生小孩
-Oh, Rach. -Screw you! You don't have to do it!
-嘿 -嘿
-Hey. -Hey!
-怎么了? -蒙娜刚刚甩了我
-What's up? -Mona just dumped me.
天啊,我很遗憾,为什么?
Oh, man, I'm sorry. Why?
最近我不是 完美男友
LateIy, I haven't exactIy been the perfect boyfriend.
我没有告诉她 我让瑞秋怀孕
I didn't teII her I got RacheI pregnant.
我给她我家的钥匙 然后换了锁
I gave her a key to my apartment and then had the Iocks changed.
我骗她 瑞秋搬到我家的事
Then I Iied to her about RacheI moving in with me.
在某方面 我怪她不早点跟我分手
In a way, I judge her for not breaking up with me sooner.
那真的很烂 特别是在情人节
That reaIIy sucks. EspeciaIIy on VaIentine's Day.
等一下 你在这里做什么?
Wait a minute. What are you doing here?
乔伊在情人节 没有约会?
Joey without a date on VaIentine's Day?
发生了什么事?你跟女人有麻烦?
What's going on, huh? GirI troubIe?
-可以那么说 -真的吗?
-Sort of. -ReaIIy?
你不必表现得这么高兴
You don't have to seem so happy about it.
或许我能帮忙
Maybe I can heIp.
不论发生了什么事 我相信我也有相同的经验
Whatever it is, I am sure it has happened to me.
事实上 我有次在做爱时被甩了
You know, actuaIIy, once I got dumped during sex.
-到底发生了什么事? -算了,没什么大不了的
-So anyway, what is it? -Forget about it. It's no big deaI.
-少来了,怎么了? -没事
-Come on, what is it? -It's nothing.
是我 你为什么不告诉我?
Hey, it's me. Why can't you teII me?
好吧,坐下
Okay. Sit down.
我很喜欢一个女人
There's this woman that I Iike a Iot.
但那是不可能的
But it can't happen.
她不会是你的姐妹吧?
She's not a Tribbiani?
不
No!
她是你的同事?
So is she someone from work?
对
Yes.
她喜欢你吗?
WeII, does she Iike you?
有时候我觉得是的
Sometimes I think she couId.
但我什么事都不能做
But I can't do anything about it.
为什么?
Why not?
事情很复杂
It's compIicated.
她跟另一个男人 交往了很久
She was with this other guy for a Iong time.
他也是我的同事
Someone from work too.
我没办法那样对他 我们是好朋友
I couId never do that to the guy. We're friends.
等一下 我以为你讨厌所有的同事
Wait, I thought you hated everyone at work.
不,我会那么说…
No, no. I onIy say that...
钱德才不会觉得被威胁了 因为我是他唯一的朋友
...so ChandIer won't feeI threatened because I'm his onIy friend.
你说什么?
Excuse me?
抱歉 我也是你唯一的朋友
Sorry, sorry. And I'm your onIy friend too.
以前跟她交往过的那个男人 还爱着她吗?
So this guy she used to go out with, is he stiII in Iove with her?
-我想应该不爱了 -好吧
-No, I don't think so. -Okay.
他是好人吗?
Is he a good guy?
对,他是最棒的
Yeah, he's the best.
-跟他谈一谈 -我不知道
-Then taIk to him. -I don't know.
如果你喜欢她 这值得试一试
It's worth finding out, if you Iike her.
我真的非常喜欢她
I do, so much.
我没办法不想到她 我睡不着…
I can't stop thinking about her. I can't sIeep--
你知道吗? 你得尽力去争取
You know what? You have to go for it.
你常遇到这种事吗? 你应该为自己这么做的
How often does this happen to you? You owe it to yourseIf.
你的温牛奶来了
Here's your warm miIk.
我要回家 加点波本酒
I'm gonna put the bourbon in it at home.
说真的 跟那个男的谈一谈,好吗?
Anyway, seriousIy, just taIk to the guy, okay?
告诉我结果
Let me know how it goes.
是瑞秋
It's RacheI.
你要生孩子了 你得做好准备
You're having a baby and you need to prepare.
你得看完整只录影带 看吧
You're gonna make yourself watch the whole thing. Just do it!
我来到这个大城市 希望成为大明星
I came to the big city to become a star.
-为了圆梦我任何事都愿意做 -任何事?
-I'll do anything to make that happen. -Anything?
或许我该从她 怎么怀孕开始看起
Maybe it starts with how she gets pregnant.
不知道哪个男人 是孩子的爸
I wonder which one of these guys becomes the father.
不 那样子是不会怀孕的
No, no. Can't get pregnant that way.